Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine Records UA235
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Student Records, 1998 -- 2018; UA235.001; 74.4 Linear Feet
  - Beaudoin, Paul E, 2012; UA235.001.034.00013 (Box 34)
  - Bednarz, Alana J, 2012; UA235.001.034.00014 (Box 34)
  - Bersson, Akiva Y, 2012; UA235.001.034.00015 (Box 34)
  - Betesh, David, 2012; UA235.001.034.00016 (Box 34)
  - Bhat, Ramya, 2012; UA235.001.034.00017 (Box 34)
  - Bland, Nicholas N, 2012; UA235.001.034.00018 (Box 34)
  - Brachowicz, Elizabeth J, 2012; UA235.001.034.00019 (Box 34)
  - Bravoco, Alexandra C, 2012; UA235.001.034.00020 (Box 34)
  - Brown, Jeffrey J, 2012; UA235.001.034.00021 (Box 34)
  - Burdick, Mathew, 2012; UA235.001.034.00022 (Box 34)
  - Carroll, Patrick F, 2012; UA235.001.034.00023 (Box 34)
  - Castle, Michael J, 2012; UA235.001.034.00024 (Box 34)
  - Chandhoke, Nirmolrattan, 2012; UA235.001.034.00025 (Box 34)
  - Chao, Gloria C, 2012; UA235.001.034.00026 (Box 34)
  - Chen, Eva K, 2012; UA235.001.034.00027 (Box 34)
  - Cho, Jai-ik, 2012; UA235.001.034.00028 (Box 34)
  - Choi, Chris Seung Kee, 2012; UA235.001.034.00029 (Box 34)
  - Cholakian, Grace, 2012; UA235.001.034.00030 (Box 34)
  - Chon, Jennifer, 2012; UA235.001.034.00031 (Box 34)
  - Costello, Michael J, 2012; UA235.001.034.00032 (Box 34)
  - Coupet, Vanessa, 2012; UA235.001.034.00033 (Box 34)
  - Covino, Julie M, 2012; UA235.001.034.00034 (Box 34)
  - Czerepak, Jonathan L, 2012; UA235.001.034.00035 (Box 34)
  - Dahl, Catherine, 2012; UA235.001.034.00036 (Box 34)
  - Dang, Nam, 2012; UA235.001.034.00037 (Box 34)
  - Darvish, Adam N, 2012; UA235.001.034.00038 (Box 34)
  - Dason, Alyss C, 2012; UA235.001.034.00039 (Box 34)
  - David, Laura K, 2012; UA235.001.034.00040 (Box 34)
  - Dawoud, Mark M, 2012; UA235.001.034.00041 (Box 34)
  - Decoteau, Corey F., 2012; UA235.001.035.00001 (Box 35)
  - DeFuria, Catherine M., 2012; UA235.001.035.00002 (Box 35)
  - DeLoach, Mary Kathryn, 2012; UA235.001.035.00003 (Box 35)
  - DeNonno, Lindsay J., 2012; UA235.001.035.00004 (Box 35)
  - DeNonno, Lindsay, 2012; UA235.001.035.00005 (Box 35)
  - DeVitre, Adrina, 2012; UA235.001.035.00006 (Box 35)
  - Dillon, Jessica R., 2012; UA235.001.035.00007 (Box 35)
  - DiNinno III, Nicholas J., 2012; UA235.001.035.00008 (Box 35)
  - Do, Hoang L., 2012; UA235.001.035.00009 (Box 35)
  - Do, Ly, 2012; UA235.001.035.00010 (Box 35)
  - Dubois, Katherine R., 2012; UA235.001.035.00011 (Box 35)
  - Duong, Kevin, 2012; UA235.001.035.00012 (Box 35)
  - Ellis, Andrew W., 2012; UA235.001.035.00013 (Box 35)
  - Ferrick, Carolyn J., 2012; UA235.001.035.00014 (Box 35)
  - Figueiredo, Daniel, 2012; UA235.001.035.00015 (Box 35)
  - Fleming, Tyler P., 2012; UA235.001.035.00016 (Box 35)
  - Foley, Bryan F., 2012; UA235.001.035.00017 (Box 35)
  - Forney, Ryan D., 2012; UA235.001.035.00018 (Box 35)
  - Fredette, Gregory A., 2012; UA235.001.035.00019 (Box 35)
  - Gil, Jose A., 2012; UA235.001.035.00020 (Box 35)
  - Goldweit, Daniel N., 2012; UA235.001.035.00021 (Box 35)
  - Gordon, Nicholas B., 2012; UA235.001.035.00022 (Box 35)
  - Greenberg, Jeffrey E., 2012; UA235.001.035.00023 (Box 35)
  - Gupte, Namrata, 2012; UA235.001.035.00024 (Box 35)
  - Jean-Marie, Sheina, 2012; UA235.001.035.00025 (Box 35)
  - Johnson, Elizabeth A., 2012; UA235.001.035.00026 (Box 35)
  - Kalka, Katarzyna, 2012; UA235.001.035.00027 (Box 35)
  - Kang, Stephanie, 2012; UA235.001.035.00028 (Box 35)
  - Kaur, Manpreet, 2012; UA235.001.035.00029 (Box 35)
  - Keithly, Inga, 2012; UA235.001.035.00030 (Box 35)
  - Hu, Lily, 2012; UA235.001.035.00031 (Box 35)
  - Huh, Shin, 2012; UA235.001.035.00032 (Box 35)
  - Hyde, Meaghan, 2012; UA235.001.035.00033 (Box 35)
  - Ip, Jonathan, 2012; UA235.001.035.00034 (Box 35)
  - Holden, Ernest E., 2012; UA235.001.035.00035 (Box 35)
  - Hornung, David G., 2012; UA235.001.035.00036 (Box 35)
  - Khankhanian, Behrod, 2012; UA235.001.035.00037 (Box 35)
  - Khankhanian, Behrod, 2012; UA235.001.035.00038 (Box 35)
  - Kim, Roy J., 2012; UA235.001.036.00001 (Box 36)
  - Kollar, Jill C., 2012; UA235.001.036.00002 (Box 36)
  - Kumata, Allison, 2012; UA235.001.036.00003 (Box 36)
  - Hassani, Omar, 2012; UA235.001.036.00004 (Box 36)
  - Hernon, Marion, 2012; UA235.001.036.00005 (Box 36)
  - Lam, Fook S., 2012; UA235.001.036.00006 (Box 36)
  - Lambalot, Lindsey M., 2012; UA235.001.036.00007 (Box 36)
  - Lazzara, David B., 2012; UA235.001.036.00008 (Box 36)
  - Leavell, Ashley R., 2012; UA235.001.036.00009 (Box 36)
  - Lee, Eunice D., 2012; UA235.001.036.00010 (Box 36)
  - Lee, Nina, 2012; UA235.001.036.00011 (Box 36)
  - Leonardi, Danielle M., 2012; UA235.001.036.00012 (Box 36)
  - Lewicki II, Albert F., 2012; UA235.001.036.00013 (Box 36)
  - Lim, Young Woo, 2012; UA235.001.036.00014 (Box 36)
  - Loo, Mitchell P., 2012; UA235.001.036.00015 (Box 36)
  - Lui, Kirsten, 2012; UA235.001.036.00016 (Box 36)
  - Massoud, Sarah M., 2012; UA235.001.036.00017 (Box 36)
  - Mathew, Treasa, 2012; UA235.001.036.00018 (Box 36)
  - McPartland, Brian P., 2012; UA235.001.036.00019 (Box 36)
  - Mello, Mary J., 2012; UA235.001.036.00020 (Box 36)
  - Miller, David T., 2012; UA235.001.036.00021 (Box 36)
  - Mitrogogos, George P., 2012; UA235.001.036.00022 (Box 36)
  - Moore, William, 2012; UA235.001.036.00023 (Box 36)
  - Moriarty, Christopher S., 2012; UA235.001.036.00024 (Box 36)
  - Mulder, Allyson B., 2012; UA235.001.036.00025 (Box 36)
  - De La Rosa, Andrew D., 2012; UA235.001.036.00026 (Box 36)
  - Muller, Paulina, 2012; UA235.001.036.00027 (Box 36)
  - Munsey, John N., 2012; UA235.001.036.00028 (Box 36)
  - Nama, Roopa P., 2012; UA235.001.036.00029 (Box 36)
  - Negron, Jonathan B., 2012; UA235.001.036.00030 (Box 36)
  - Neill, Noelle, 2012; UA235.001.036.00031 (Box 36)
  - Newton, Kimberly M., 2012; UA235.001.036.00032 (Box 36)
  - Ngo, Vi T., 2012; UA235.001.036.00033 (Box 36)
  - Nguyen, Amy D., 2012; UA235.001.036.00034 (Box 36)
  - Nguyen, Le, 2012; UA235.001.037.00001 (Box 37)
  - Nicholas, Ann R., 2012; UA235.001.037.00002 (Box 37)
  - Nix, Jacob A., 2012; UA235.001.037.00003 (Box 37)
  - Nobrega, Derek A., 2012; UA235.001.037.00004 (Box 37)
  - Nunes, Martin R., 2012; UA235.001.037.00005 (Box 37)
  - Ogledzki, Marek J., 2012; UA235.001.037.00006 (Box 37)
  - Oh, Jin Sub, 2012; UA235.001.037.00007 (Box 37)
  - Pakula, Emily J., 2012; UA235.001.037.00008 (Box 37)
  - Pare', Elizabeth A., 2012; UA235.001.037.00009 (Box 37)
  - Park, James, 2012; UA235.001.037.00010 (Box 37)
  - Park, Jill, 2012; UA235.001.037.00011 (Box 37)
  - Patel, Binita, 2012; UA235.001.037.00012 (Box 37)
  - Patel, Megha, 2012; UA235.001.037.00013 (Box 37)
  - Pedersen, Colin W., 2012; UA235.001.037.00014 (Box 37)
  - Perdomo Jr., Mauro D., 2012; UA235.001.037.00015 (Box 37)
  - Pimentel, Arlene S., 2012; UA235.001.037.00016 (Box 37)
  - Pishtari, Jonila, 2012; UA235.001.037.00017 (Box 37)
  - Plumley, John, 2012; UA235.001.037.00018 (Box 37)
  - Price, Lauren E., 2012; UA235.001.037.00019 (Box 37)
  - Pushee, Jessica L., 2012; UA235.001.037.00020 (Box 37)
  - Rozdolski, Raquel M., 2012; UA235.001.037.00021 (Box 37)
  - Ruparelia, Urvi N., 2012; UA235.001.037.00022 (Box 37)
  - Saferin, Tori, 2012; UA235.001.037.00023 (Box 37)
  - Salem, Muhanad A., 2012; UA235.001.037.00024 (Box 37)
  - Secor, Camille, 2012; UA235.001.037.00025 (Box 37)
  - Shah, Devina S., 2012; UA235.001.037.00026 (Box 37)
  - Shah, Dhaval V., 2012; UA235.001.037.00027 (Box 37)
  - Shah, Sagar M., 2012; UA235.001.037.00028 (Box 37)
    International Student
  - Shahnaz, Pourya, 2012; UA235.001.037.00029 (Box 37)
  - Shakourian, Golbarg N., 2012; UA235.001.037.00030 (Box 37)
  - Singh, Paul N., 2012; UA235.001.037.00031 (Box 37)
  - Skalina, Nicole, 2012; UA235.001.037.00032 (Box 37)
  - Slomovitz, Steven B., 2012; UA235.001.037.00033 (Box 37)
  - Snow, Jesse, 2012; UA235.001.037.00034 (Box 37)
  - Sosna, Marlayna C., 2012; UA235.001.037.00035 (Box 37)
  - Stakes, Marina C., 2012; UA235.001.037.00036 (Box 37)
  - Stetsyuk, Victor, 2012; UA235.001.037.00037 (Box 37)
  - Stevanovic, Marko, 2012; UA235.001.037.00038 (Box 37)
  - Stolch, Krista A., 2012; UA235.001.037.00039 (Box 37)
  - Terrassa, Isabella, 2012; UA235.001.038.00001 (Box 38)
  - Timmeny, Maureen B., 2012; UA235.001.038.00002 (Box 38)
  - Toland, Meghan R., 2012; UA235.001.038.00003 (Box 38)
  - Tran, Phu N., 2012; UA235.001.038.00004 (Box 38)
  - Tran, Thien V., 2012; UA235.001.038.00005 (Box 38)
  - Tripodakis, Dimitri, 2012; UA235.001.038.00006 (Box 38)
  - Trahan, William R., 2012; UA235.001.038.00007 (Box 38)
  - Velasquez, Fernando, 2012; UA235.001.038.00008 (Box 38)
  - Wasserman, Lee H., 2012; UA235.001.038.00009 (Box 38)
  - Welnak, John P., 2012; UA235.001.038.00010 (Box 38)
  - Welnak, Thomas M., 2012; UA235.001.038.00011 (Box 38)
  - Xie, Eileen P., 2012; UA235.001.038.00012 (Box 38)
  - Yoo, Kyungsuk, 2012; UA235.001.038.00013 (Box 38)
  - Yu, Serena J., 2012; UA235.001.038.00014 (Box 38)
  - Yunes, Scott B., 2012; UA235.001.038.00015 (Box 38)
  - Hur, Yong, 2012; UA235.001.038.00016
  - Hur, Yong, 2012; UA235.001.038.00017
  - Hur,Yong, 2012; UA235.001.038.00018
  - Hur, Yong, 2012; UA235.001.038.00019
  - Chikersal, Simita, 2012; UA235.001.038.00020 (Box 38)
  - Dhillon, Shubhpreet K., 2012; UA235.001.038.00021 (Box 38)
  - Dukas, Carla F., 2012; UA235.001.038.00022 (Box 38)
  - Giraldo, Jhon O., 2012; UA235.001.038.00023 (Box 38)
  - Giri, Meenu, 2012; UA235.001.038.00024 (Box 38)
  - Khan, Nikhat P., 2012; UA235.001.038.00025 (Box 38)
  - Khedher, Hawazin, 2012; UA235.001.038.00026 (Box 38)
  - Milani, Mandana B., 2012; UA235.001.038.00027 (Box 38)
  - Narli-Trangaris, Esin, 2012; UA235.001.038.00028 (Box 38)
  - Patel, Gaurangkumar, 2012; UA235.001.038.00029 (Box 38)
  - Sakhamuri, Saranya, 2012; UA235.001.038.00030 (Box 38)
  - Sharma, Sushen, 2012; UA235.001.038.00031 (Box 38)
  - Singh, Baljinder, 2012; UA235.001.038.00032 (Box 38)
  - Ajala, Joachim, 2001; UA235.001.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - Bhagwat, Jui R., 2001; UA235.001.039.00002 (Box 39)
  - Boppana, Sridevi, 2000; UA235.001.039.00003 (Box 39)
  - Buttar, Navkiran, 2001; UA235.001.039.00004 (Box 39)
  - Cardenas, Cesar, 2001; UA235.001.039.00005 (Box 39)
  - Chen, Jiwen, 2001; UA235.001.039.00006 (Box 39)
  - Davila, Julian E., 2001; UA235.001.039.00007 (Box 39)
  - Dhanekula, Madhavi, 2000; UA235.001.039.00008 (Box 39)
  - Lally, Lorna F., 2001; UA235.001.039.00009 (Box 39)
  - Lee, Wonjae, 2001; UA235.001.039.00010 (Box 39)
  - Liu, Lidong, 1999; UA235.001.039.00011 (Box 39)
  - Liu, Manhui, 2001; UA235.001.039.00012 (Box 39)
  - Nathan, Maya R., 1998; UA235.001.039.00013 (Box 39)
  - Suri, Lokesh, 2001; UA235.001.039.00014 (Box 39)
  - Tabbah, Michael, 2001; UA235.001.039.00015 (Box 39)
  - Wang, Joao L., 2001; UA235.001.039.00016 (Box 39)
  - Wang, Yan, 2001; UA235.001.039.00017 (Box 39)
  - Yang, Dongmei, 2001; UA235.001.039.00018 (Box 39)
  - Vu, Lamb D., 2001; UA235.001.039.00019 (Box 39)
  - Wells, Christopher, 2001; UA235.001.039.00020 (Box 39)
  - Wietecha, Jay R., 2000; UA235.001.039.00021 (Box 39)
  - Woo, Young H., 2001; UA235.001.039.00022 (Box 39)
  - Wu, Theodore K., 2001; UA235.001.039.00023 (Box 39)
  - Yee, Howard G., 2001; UA235.001.039.00024 (Box 39)
  - Yu, Wilfred, 2001; UA235.001.039.00025 (Box 39)
  - Zopf, Aimee M., 2000; UA235.001.039.00026 (Box 39)
  - Kalis, Catherine A., 2003; UA235.001.039.00027 (Box 39)
  - Kaneyoshi, Taketo, 2003; UA235.001.039.00028 (Box 39)
  - Karacosta, Olympia, 2007; UA235.001.039.00029 (Box 39)
  - Kazemifar, Hoda, 2003; UA235.001.039.00030 (Box 39)
  - Kiecker, Jessica L., 2002; UA235.001.039.00031 (Box 39)
  - Kim, James Y., 2003; UA235.001.039.00032 (Box 39)
  - Kim, Sarah, 2003; UA235.001.039.00033 (Box 39)
  - Hill, Jennifer K., 2003; UA235.001.039.00034 (Box 39)
  - Komarovskaya, Inna O., 2003; UA235.001.039.00035 (Box 39)
  - Krol, Jolene A., 2003; UA235.001.039.00036 (Box 39)
  - Kudchadkar, Durgesh A., 2003; UA235.001.039.00037 (Box 39)
  - Lai, Yen-Tseng, 2003; UA235.001.039.00038 (Box 39)
  - Landa, Jorge E., 2003; UA235.001.039.00039 (Box 39)
  - Le, Bao-Quyen T., 2003; UA235.001.039.00040 (Box 39)
  - Le, Trang T., 2003; UA235.001.039.00041 (Box 39)
  - Lee, Yvonne, 2003; UA235.001.039.00042 (Box 39)
  - Ling, Lily A., 2003; UA235.001.039.00043 (Box 39)
  - Lo, John, 2003; UA235.001.039.00044 (Box 39)
  - Loehr, Brendan B., 2002; UA235.001.039.00045 (Box 39)
  - Lu, Iu J., 2003; UA235.001.039.00046 (Box 39)
  - Macini, Ann Marie, 2003; UA235.001.039.00047 (Box 39)
  - Markos, Theodoros, 2007; UA235.001.039.00048 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Nichole C., 2003; UA235.001.039.00049 (Box 39)
  - McAdams, Tiffany A., 2002; UA235.001.039.00050 (Box 39)
  - McNear, Nicole C., 2003; UA235.001.039.00051 (Box 39)
  - McTernan, Erin A., 2003; UA235.001.039.00052 (Box 39)
  - Mheta, Rahul, 2003; UA235.001.039.00053 (Box 39)
  - Shenoy, Sangeeta, 2003; UA235.001.039.00054 (Box 39)
  - Merrell, David A., 2003; UA235.001.039.00055 (Box 39)
  - Merrell, Jill Y., 2007; UA235.001.039.00056 (Box 39)
  - Miranda, Joshua O., 2003; UA235.001.039.00057 (Box 39)
  - Montgomery, Aimee L., 2003; UA235.001.039.00058 (Box 39)
  - Montoya, Edward L., 2003; UA235.001.040.00001 (Box 40)
  - Moon, Young J., 2003; UA235.001.040.00002 (Box 40)
  - Murray II, Nicholas J., 2003; UA235.001.040.00003 (Box 40)
  - Nguyen, Hong L., 2003; UA235.001.040.00004 (Box 40)
  - Nguyen, Hong T., 2003; UA235.001.040.00005 (Box 40)
  - Nguyen, Thien C., 2003; UA235.001.040.00006 (Box 40)
  - Noga, Lori A., 2003; UA235.001.040.00007 (Box 40)
  - O'Shea, Lewis, 2007; UA235.001.040.00008 (Box 40)
  - Osofsky, Renee, 2007; UA235.001.040.00009 (Box 40)
  - Park, Jin, 2003; UA235.001.040.00010 (Box 40)
  - Park, Youn Joo, 2005; UA235.001.040.00011 (Box 40)
  - Parvinjah, Farbod, 2003; UA235.001.040.00012 (Box 40)
  - Paskalev, Ivan, 2005; UA235.001.040.00013 (Box 40)
  - Pasquale, Anthony F., 2003; UA235.001.040.00014 (Box 40)
  - Patel, Shefali V., 2002; UA235.001.040.00015 (Box 40)
  - Patel, Shruti J., 2003; UA235.001.040.00016 (Box 40)
  - Pellino, Katerina, 2001; UA235.001.040.00017 (Box 40)
  - Peterman, John L., 2003; UA235.001.040.00018 (Box 40)
  - Pham, Cindey N., 2003; UA235.001.040.00019 (Box 40)
  - Phan, Peter T., 2003; UA235.001.040.00020 (Box 40)
  - Pierse, Joseph, 2003; UA235.001.040.00021 (Box 40)
  - Pyon, Kwang R., 2002; UA235.001.040.00022 (Box 40)
  - Rastogi, Sachin, 2005; UA235.001.040.00023 (Box 40)
  - Ravago, Melissa, 2003; UA235.001.040.00024 (Box 40)
  - Reese, Chad S., 2003; UA235.001.040.00025 (Box 40)
  - Rolf, Erin, 2003; UA235.001.040.00026 (Box 40)
  - Bouvier, Melissa A., 2003; UA235.001.040.00027 (Box 40)
  - Rosato, Christine A., 2003; UA235.001.040.00028 (Box 40)
  - Ross II, William A., 2003; UA235.001.040.00029 (Box 40)
  - Rubinov, Konstantin, 2007; UA235.001.040.00030 (Box 40)
  - Salinas, Felipe, 2002; UA235.001.040.00031 (Box 40)
  - Satar, Ramez, 2003; UA235.001.040.00032 (Box 40)
  - Sawhney, Arvinder, 2005; UA235.001.040.00033 (Box 40)
  - Schwarz, Elan B., 2003; UA235.001.040.00034 (Box 40)
  - Scott, John S., 2002; UA235.001.040.00035 (Box 40)
  - Scott, Justin S., 2003; UA235.001.040.00036 (Box 40)
  - Segnere, Jeffrey M., 2003; UA235.001.040.00037 (Box 40)
  - Seo, Jong-Bum J., 2003; UA235.001.040.00038 (Box 40)
  - Shah, Puja, 2006; UA235.001.040.00039 (Box 40)
  - Shahmardi, Siamak, 2003; UA235.001.040.00040 (Box 40)
  - Sheikh, Shazia M., 2003; UA235.001.040.00041 (Box 40)
  - Singh, Mabi L., 2007; UA235.001.040.00042 (Box 40)
  - Siu, Kayee, 2003; UA235.001.040.00043 (Box 40)
  - Slaughter, Lisa A., 2003; UA235.001.040.00044 (Box 40)
  - Smart, Ryan J., 2003; UA235.001.040.00045 (Box 40)
  - Souza, Jauna L., 2003; UA235.001.040.00046 (Box 40)
  - Spencer, Daniel J., 2002; UA235.001.040.00047 (Box 40)
  - Szwec-Levin, Yonit, 2007; UA235.001.040.00048 (Box 40)
  - Tang, Sopheap, 2003; UA235.001.040.00049 (Box 40)
  - Tariq, Nomaan, 2003; UA235.001.040.00050 (Box 40)
  - Torres, Jose, 2002; UA235.001.040.00051 (Box 40)
  - Tran, Quan Ahn, 2003; UA235.001.040.00052 (Box 40)
  - Troupe, Emilie M., 2003; UA235.001.040.00053 (Box 40)
  - Tsai, Judy Chai Ling, 2003; UA235.001.040.00054 (Box 40)
  - Vargas, Joanne C., 2003; UA235.001.040.00055 (Box 40)
  - Venkatappa Ramadas, Shamantha, 2005; UA235.001.040.00056 (Box 40)
  - Wiegand, Amanda D., 2003; UA235.001.040.00057 (Box 40)
  - Wilson, Piper E., 2003; UA235.001.040.00058 (Box 40)
  - Yang, Hyon-Mo, 2003; UA235.001.040.00059 (Box 40)
  - Yoon, Young J., 2002; UA235.001.040.00060 (Box 40)
  - Young, Caroline, 2007; UA235.001.040.00061 (Box 40)
  - Zaenchik, Valerie A., 2003; UA235.001.040.00062 (Box 40)
  - Zervou, Christina, 2007; UA235.001.040.00063 (Box 40)
  - Zhang, Ning, 2003; UA235.001.040.00064 (Box 40)
  - Macway, Sara, 2005; UA235.001.041.00001 (Box 41)
  - Marin, Claudiu, 2005; UA235.001.041.00002 (Box 41)
  - Mathew, Jeslin S., 2005; UA235.001.041.00003 (Box 41)
  - McLean, Eric A., 2005; UA235.001.041.00004 (Box 41)
  - McManus, Erin E., 2005; UA235.001.041.00005 (Box 41)
  - Mithani, Bansi, 2009; UA235.001.041.00006 (Box 41)
  - Mojarrad, Nasem, 2005; UA235.001.041.00007 (Box 41)
  - Moshier, James A., 2005; UA235.001.041.00008 (Box 41)
  - Murphy, James P., 2005; UA235.001.041.00009 (Box 41)
  - Murphy, Raymond M., 2005; UA235.001.041.00010 (Box 41)
  - Naik, Sonal A., 2005; UA235.001.041.00011 (Box 41)
  - Nasir, Aisha, 2007; UA235.001.041.00012 (Box 41)
  - Navidomskis, Mathhew T., 2004; UA235.001.041.00013 (Box 41)
  - Nessim, Michael M., 2007; UA235.001.041.00014 (Box 41)
  - Ngo, Yen B., 2004; UA235.001.041.00015 (Box 41)
  - Nguyen, Cassandra H., 2005; UA235.001.041.00016 (Box 41)
  - Nguyen, Dung N., 2004; UA235.001.041.00017 (Box 41)
  - Oh, BiNa, 2009; UA235.001.041.00018 (Box 41)
  - Orinda, Noreen A., 2004; UA235.001.041.00019 (Box 41)
  - Overson, Jonathan C., 2004; UA235.001.041.00020 (Box 41)
  - Palmer, Erin R., 2004; UA235.001.041.00021 (Box 41)
  - Pappu, Aruna, 2006; UA235.001.041.00022 (Box 41)
  - Passarella, Sarah Ann, 2009; UA235.001.041.00023 (Box 41)
  - Patel, Ekta, 2009; UA235.001.041.00024 (Box 41)
  - Patel, Nisha C., 2005; UA235.001.041.00025 (Box 41)
  - Patt, Marisa E., 2005; UA235.001.041.00026 (Box 41)
  - Pechter, Joesph E., 2004; UA235.001.041.00027 (Box 41)
  - Perham, Kate E., 2005; UA235.001.041.00028 (Box 41)
  - Perry, Chelsea E., 2005; UA235.001.041.00029 (Box 41)
  - Piascik, Eric G., 2004; UA235.001.041.00030 (Box 41)
  - Pirpiris, Demi Z., 2004; UA235.001.041.00031 (Box 41)
  - Pokrovskaya, Nadezhda D., 2004; UA235.001.041.00032 (Box 41)
  - Preminger, Joel M., 2004; UA235.001.041.00033 (Box 41)
  - Ramdah, Antoitette, 2009; UA235.001.041.00034 (Box 41)
  - Ramos, Sahana, 2007; UA235.001.041.00035 (Box 41)
  - Rastogi, Geetika, 2005; UA235.001.041.00036 (Box 41)
  - Raynor, Jason R., 2004; UA235.001.041.00037 (Box 41)
  - Reeson, Shana L., 2004; UA235.001.041.00038 (Box 41)
  - Rexford, Ashleigh M., 2005; UA235.001.041.00039 (Box 41)
  - Rizk, Susan, 2005; UA235.001.041.00040 (Box 41)
  - Roskelley, Jacob D., 2005; UA235.001.041.00041 (Box 41)
  - Roskelley, Lindsay C., 2005; UA235.001.041.00042 (Box 41)
  - Rosse, Hillary E., 2005; UA235.001.041.00043 (Box 41)
  - Rostami, Mahsa, 2005; UA235.001.041.00044 (Box 41)
  - Roumani, Leila, 2005; UA235.001.041.00045 (Box 41)
  - Saltman, Jane M., 2005; UA235.001.041.00046 (Box 41)
  - Schiller, Robin J., 2005; UA235.001.041.00047 (Box 41)
  - Schirmer, Kathryn L., 2005; UA235.001.041.00048 (Box 41)
  - Schuessler, Adam D, 2005; UA235.001.041.00049 (Box 41)
  - Seo, Kyung Won, 2004; UA235.001.041.00050 (Box 41)
  - Shah, Aekta, 2009; UA235.001.041.00051 (Box 41)
  - Sharma, Meera, 2007; UA235.001.041.00052 (Box 41)
  - Sheinfeld, Aaron, 2009; UA235.001.041.00053 (Box 41)
  - Shenk, Elizabeth G., 2005; UA235.001.041.00054 (Box 41)
  - Shin, Mose, 2004; UA235.001.042.00001 (Box 42)
  - Slomovitz, Jason P., 2005; UA235.001.042.00002 (Box 42)
  - Smith, Emily S., 2005; UA235.001.042.00003 (Box 42)
  - Sripathi, Radhika, 2007; UA235.001.042.00004 (Box 42)
  - Stanger, Ryan T., 2004; UA235.001.042.00005 (Box 42)
  - Tarassoli, Yasamin, 2007; UA235.001.042.00006 (Box 42)
  - Tarver, Michael, 2005; UA235.001.042.00007 (Box 42)
  - Thakkar, Dhaval B., 2005; UA235.001.042.00008 (Box 42)
  - Tippi Reddy, Surender Reddy, 2007; UA235.001.042.00009 (Box 42)
  - Tiwana, Sabeen, 2007; UA235.001.042.00010 (Box 42)
  - Tran, Lee T., 2005; UA235.001.042.00011 (Box 42)
  - Tsomo, Lobsang, 2004; UA235.001.042.00012 (Box 42)
  - Turkat, Holly D., 2005; UA235.001.042.00013 (Box 42)
  - Vasanth, Supriya S., 2007; UA235.001.042.00014 (Box 42)
  - Vaughn, Andrew J., 2005; UA235.001.042.00015 (Box 42)
  - Vayanos, Peter G., 2004; UA235.001.042.00016 (Box 42)
  - Warner, Brian C., 2005; UA235.001.042.00017 (Box 42)
  - Wei, Yi Chen, 2005; UA235.001.042.00018 (Box 42)
  - White, Caitlin E., 2005; UA235.001.042.00019 (Box 42)
  - Wimmer, Matthew R., 2004; UA235.001.042.00020 (Box 42)
  - Wong, Erik K., 2005; UA235.001.042.00021 (Box 42)
  - Wu, Dayang, 2007; UA235.001.042.00022 (Box 42)
  - Young, Julia M., 2005; UA235.001.042.00023 (Box 42)
  - Younis, Leah M., 2005; UA235.001.042.00024 (Box 42)
  - Yu, Fan, 2007; UA235.001.042.00025 (Box 42)
  - Zaygermakher, Karina, 2005; UA235.001.042.00026 (Box 42)
  - Student Information Cards, 2007; UA235.001.042.00027 (Box 42)
  - Student Information Cards [1 of 2], 2009; UA235.001.042.00028 (Box 42)
  - Student Information Cards [2 of 2], 2009; UA235.001.042.00029 (Box 42)
  - Student Personal Data and Registration Forms, 2006; UA235.001.042.00030 (Box 42)
  - Student Personal Data and Registration Forms, 2008; UA235.001.042.00031 (Box 42)
  - Ahn, Doksoo, 2002; UA235.001.042.00032 (Box 42)
  - Hassan, Mohamed M. [1 of 2], 2004; UA235.001.042.00033 (Box 42)
  - Hassan, Mohamed M. [2 of 2], 2004; UA235.001.042.00034 (Box 42)
  - Al-Mashan, Abdullah, 2008; UA235.001.042.00035 (Box 42)
  - Blanchi, Thomas C., 2008; UA235.001.042.00036 (Box 42)
  - Yoon, Jong Won, 2009; UA235.001.042.00037 (Box 42)
  - Belden, Amanda G., 2010; UA235.001.042.00038 (Box 42)
  - Butera, Michael R., 2010; UA235.001.042.00039 (Box 42)
  - Cordero Andujar, Stephany M., 2011; UA235.001.042.00040 (Box 42)
  - Student Questionaires, 2008; UA235.001.048.00027 (Box UA235 Shared 1)
  - Abuzaineh, Omar M., 2013; UA235.001.075.00001 (Box 75)
  - Ackerman, Heidi A., 2013; UA235.001.075.00002 (Box 75)
  - Ahn, Chanook D., 2013; UA235.001.075.00003 (Box 75)
  - Aldo, Natasha, 2013; UA235.001.075.00004 (Box 75)
  - Alikpala, C Marissa R., 2013; UA235.001.075.00005 (Box 75)
  - Allatabakhsh, Amir, 2013; UA235.001.075.00006 (Box 75)
  - Al-Kharsa, Saleh S., 2013; UA235.001.075.00007 (Box 75)
  - Assadi-Moghadam, Assal, 2013; UA235.001.075.00008 (Box 75)
  - Bair, Jin-Hwei Julianna S, 2013; UA235.001.075.00009 (Box 75)
  - Beck, Brian R., 2013; UA235.001.075.00010 (Box 75)
  - Bello, Nicholas G., 2013; UA235.001.075.00011 (Box 75)
  - Biewer, Michelle M., 2013; UA235.001.075.00012 (Box 75)
  - Black, Kevin L., 2013; UA235.001.075.00013 (Box 75)
  - Boehm, Austin, 2013; UA235.001.075.00014 (Box 75)
  - Bond, Dustin A., 2013; UA235.001.075.00015 (Box 75)
  - Brangwynne, Lindsey J., 2013; UA235.001.075.00016 (Box 75)
  - Brayley, Brett M., 2013; UA235.001.075.00017 (Box 75)
  - Brown, Ashley A., 2013; UA235.001.075.00018 (Box 75)
  - Brubaker, Ashley L., 2013; UA235.001.075.00019 (Box 75)
  - Burke, Kevin J., 2013; UA235.001.075.00020 (Box 75)
  - Cagliostro, Stephenn N., 2013; UA235.001.075.00021 (Box 75)
  - Camacho, Diego A., 2013; UA235.001.075.00022 (Box 75)
  - Cao, Christine J., 2013; UA235.001.075.00023 (Box 75)
  - Cataldo, Carmine S., 2013; UA235.001.075.00024 (Box 75)
  - Chang, Calvin, 2013; UA235.001.075.00025 (Box 75)
  - Chang, Peter K., 2012; UA235.001.075.00026 (Box 75)
  - Chau, Jennifer, 2013; UA235.001.075.00027 (Box 75)